Anywhere you are, distance is not a barrier.
Viewers, you are called to battle the spiritual entities which cause crisis in your lives.
You and Prophet T.B Joshua together, in the name of Jesus,
can stop satan killing, stealing and destroying your life.
Touch the screen right now.
Be engaged with God.
I want to pray with the viewers right now
Those who are under the influence of my voice.
Whatever situation that you are in,
I say, be released, in the name of Jesus!
Viewers all over the world, whatever situation that you are in -
it is not the will of God.
Be released, in theme of Jesus!
It is the will of God to release you and I release you, in the name of Jesus!
Listen, the voice of God says -
you are released, in the name of Jesus!
The voice of God says -
Yes, I will not blame you, that you are doubting.
Your doubt will not change anything.
Viewers, listen! You are doubting that;
‘Is that how I will be released? I have suffered so much’.
I say, you are released, in the name of Jesus!
Your doubt will not change anything.
Be released!
Whatever the situation – it could be hardship, setback, depression, affliction,
I say, be released in the name of Jesus!
I can see you being released.
A prophet says he can see you being released.
Viewers, what does this mean to you?
I want to hear from you, what does this mean to you?
What does it mean to you?
If you honour a prophet because he is a prophet of God,
you will receive his reward.
A prophet says right now, you are released.
What does it mean to you?
You are delivered.
You are healed.
What does it mean to you?
You are free.
You are saved.
What does it mean to you?
In Jesus' name!
Yes!
That is the confession God wants to hear -
that when a prophet says you are released, what does it mean to you?
You say, you are released. That is all.
From your mouth, faith comes.
'Yes, yes' - comes faith.
'No, no' - comes doubt.
We leave you under the influence of the Holy Spirit and pray to meet you there again
Allow your heart to be deeply engaged with God as you send your testimony
We believe you have been inspired by the clip that you just have watched
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up to date with the latest prophesies, deliverances, service and testimonies
from the Synagogue Church Of All Nations.
Emmanuel TV - changing lives, changing nations, and changing the world
CR Robert Begier 16/04/2019